Guide to the Brian Lassiter Hip Hop Collection, circa 1980-2013.
Lassiter, Brian Hip Hop Collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Brian Lassiter Hip Hop Collection, circa 1980-2013.
8106
Lassiter, Brian,
35
Photographs, printed material, financial records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Magazines, books, photographs, flyers, posters, label and artist promotional press packets, business records, and music sales and distribution catalogs document numerous Hip Hop artists and events, particularly in Atlanta and throughout the South.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Brian Lassiter was an active figure in Atlanta's Hip Hop and rap music scene. His career has spanned across jobs as an audio engineer, camera operator, and journalist, and as a small business owner focused on artist management and promotion, music production, marketing, sales and distribution.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Magazines, books, photographs, flyers, posters, label and artist promotional press packets, business records, and music sales and distribution catalogs document numerous Hip Hop artists and events, particularly in Atlanta and throughout the South. Nearly 2,000 issues of national and regional Hip Hop and urban music magazines chronicle the rise and spread of Hip Hop culture, and its specific look and sound as it emerged in different regions of the country. The collection is especially strong in the 1980s, 1990s, and the early 2000s - the era before online content began to suppress the number and variety of paper publications. The archive provides information about urban arts, music, entertainment, and the black alternative press during the last quarter of the 20th century and the early years of the 21st.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Lassiter, Brian,
Subjects:
Hip-hop.; Rap (Music); African American entertainers; African American journalists; African American press; African Americans; African American musicians
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Series V. Magazines and Periodicals, by appointment pending completion of processing.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Notebooks
Box 1-2
Series II. Business Files
Boxes 3-5
Business Plans, Receipts, and Invoices
General Business Files
Business Listings and Catalog Magazines
Equipment and Services
Series III. Publicity and Advertising
Box 6-9, Mapcase Folder 1
General
Press Packets
Mixed Press Materials
Magazines, Newsletters, and Photos
Movies and Television
Investment Packets and Marketing Plans
Loose Posters and Flyers
Series IV. Media
Box 2
CDs and DVDs
Cassette Tapes
VHS Videos
Series V. Lassiter Hip-Hop and Music Related Magazine and Periodical Collection
Boxes 2, 10-65
Booklets
Magazines and other Periodicals
Titles A-H
Titles I-O
Titles P-Z
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Notebooks
  Mainly consist of daily notes. Other entries noted.
  Arranged by size and then by date
  - 4 small undated notebooks, undated (Box 1)
    daily lists & contact information
  - 5 undated 6x9 80 sheet notebooks, undated (Box 1)
  - 3 undated 6x9 150 sheet notebooks, undated (Box 1)
    primarily contain locations
  - Atlanta notes, 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - Miami notes, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Small 1987 notebook, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Miami notes, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Tuff City notes, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Powerlord Records 1992 "Disco Houndz", 1992 (Box 1)
  - Small 1996 notebook, 1996 (Box 1)
    primarily addresses
  - Small 2003 notebook, 2003 (Box 1)
    primarily lists of stores and phone numbers
  - 5 small 2005 notebooks, 2005 (Box 1)
  - Small April 2005 notebook, April 2005 (Box 1)
  - Small Fall 2005 notebook, Fall 2005 (Box 1)
  - 2 small 2006 notebooks, 2006 (Box 1)
    phone numbers
  - 3 small 2007 notebooks, 2007 (Box 1)
  - dbII, Regional Retail Promotion & Tracking, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Downstairs Productions, World Premiere Records, Jupiter Hill Music/BMI, 1986 (Box 1)
    lists of songs, records, sound effects, shows, equipment
  - January 1996 (Box 1)
  - September 1996 (Box 1)
  - October-November 1996 (Box 1)
  - December 1996 (Box 1)
  - January-February 1997 (Box 1)
  - March 1997 (Box 1)
  - April 1997 (Box 1)
  - June 1997 (Box 1)
  - July-August 1997 (Box 1)
  - September 1997 (Box 1)
  - October-November 1997 (Box 1)
  - December 1997 (Box 1)
  - June-August 1998 (Box 1)
  - September 1998 (Box 1)
  - "Calendars" notepad, October-November 1998 (Box 1)
  - December 1998 (Box 1)
  - March-April 1999 (Box 1)
  - May 1999 (Box 1)
  - July 1999 (Box 1)
  - August 1999 (Box 1)
  - October 1999 (Box 1)
  - October-November 1999 (Box 1)
  - November-December 1999 (Box 1)
  - January 2000 (Box 1)
  - February-March 2000 (Box 1)
  - April-May 2000 (Box 1)
  - June-July 2000 (Box 1)
  - August-September 2000 (Box 1)
  - November-December 2000 (Box 1)
  - January 2001 (Box 1)
  - May 2001 (Box 1)
  - "Niat & Dads Notebook", undated (Box 1)
  - Undated Notebook, undated (Box 1)
  - Undated Notebook, undated (Box 1)
  - 2005; 1998; March 13, 2006; February 9, 1998 (Box 1)
    most entries undated
  - January 1995; February 1995; "May", "June" (Box 1)
  - 2000; March 1999 (Box 1)
  - October-November 1995 (Box 1)
  - Pyramid Records Group (phone calls), November 11, 1994 - February 17, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Pyramid Records Group (phone calls) #2, February 17, 1995 - May 28, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Pyramid Records Group (phone calls) #3, May 18 - August 22 (Box 2)
  - World Premiere Records, August 22 - November 14 (Box 2)
  - November 1995, January 1995 (Box 2)
  - World Premiere Records, January 16, 1996 - April 5, 1996 (Box 2)
  - 1, April 1996 (Box 2)
  - 2, July 1996 (Box 2)
  - 3, September 1996 (Box 2)
  - 1, December 26, 1996 - March 17, 1997 (Box 2)
  - 2, March 1997 - June 1997 (Box 2)
  - 3, June 1997 - August 26, 1997 (Box 2)
  - 4, August 26, 1997 - November 22, 1997 (Box 2)
  - 5, November 1997 - February 1998 (Box 2)
  - February 26, 1998 - May 28, 1998 (Box 2)
  - June 1, 1998 - August 26, 1998 (Box 2)
  - August 26, 1998 - December 1998 (Box 2)
  - January 1999 - March 29, 1999 (Box 2)
  - March 30, 1999 - June 30, 1999 (Box 2)
  - July 1, 1999 - October 7, 1999 (Box 2)
  - October 7, 1999 - January 9, 2000 (Box 2)
  - April 10, 2000 - July 9, 2000 (Box 2)
  - January 10, 2000 - April 10, 2000 (Box 2)
  - July 10, 2000 - October 8, 2000 (Box 2)
  - October 9, 2000 - January 13, 2001 (Box 2)
- Series II. Business Files
  - Business Plans, Receipts, and Invoices
    - Contracts, 1989-1996, 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Juniper Hill Contracts, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Business Plans, 1996-1999, 2003, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Business Plans, 1996, 1998, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Studio Receipts, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Invoices, September 1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Receipts and Invoices, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      includes some correspondence
    - Sales Receipts from the Album Midwest Funk Soundtrack, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Invoices, January 1996 - April 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Invoices, May 1996 - July 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Invoices, August 1996 - September 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Invoices, October 1996 - December 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Invoices, January 1997 - February 1997 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Invoices, February 1997 - May 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Invoices, June 1997 - September 1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Invoices, October 1997 - December 1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Invoices, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Purchase Orders and Invoices, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Invoices, 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Sample Forms, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - NY State Map, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Business Cards and News clippings, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - General Business Files
    - Music Business Binder (1), 1981-1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Music Business Binder (2), 1979-1999 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Music Business Binder (3), 1983-2005 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - SRS: Songwriters Resources and Services, 1978-1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Business Files, 1980, 1991-2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Correspondence, retail lists, invoices
    - Business Files, 1985-2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Ads, newspaper & magazine clippings
    - Business Files, 1986, 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Correspondence, invoices, retail lists
    - Business Files, 1986, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Correspondence, magazine copies/clippings
    - Kiss 104 Materials, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Invoices, playlists, ads, event data
    - Business Files, 1987-1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Correspondence, map, news clippings, advertisements, pricing list
    - Business Files, 1987, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Correspondence, press release, sample form
    - Business Files, ca. 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      News and magazine copies, drafts of articles
    - Business Files, ca. 1994-2003 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Correspondence, newsletters, news clippings, list of top 100 singles, manual
    - Business Files, ca. 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Retail lists, invoices, publication and advertising information
    - Business Files, ca. 1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Newspaper clippings, magazine copies, record lists
    - Southern Music, 1988-1989, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Ticket stubs, schedules for label forums, memo about music compilation, article about disc jockeys
    - Howard University, Black History, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989, 1993, 2000, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Correspondence, article about Black Hand Entertainment, invoice for Islam publications, pamphlet on Islam
    - Pyramid Records Fan Club, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Music Surveys for Rickett's Records, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Idea Notes, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Business Listings and Catalog Magazines
    - Distributor Lists, Vendor Cost Profiles, 1988-1989, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Retail Mailing Lists, ca. 1994, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      Includes a poster invoice from 2001, Platinum World Records business card
    - "B Files", undated; CD-2651 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Luke Records Retail List, January 7, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Music Distributors Mailing List, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - The Green Pages First Quarter 1987, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Hip Hop Roundup, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      Photocopied, with note "This is a good reference"
    - Nova Distributing Corp. Top Selling Discos, September 5, 1986; June 26, 1987; February 12, 1988; April 22, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Lists of record shops, distributors and radio stations, 1993, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - List of Radio Stations with cities and Telephone Numbers, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Black Pages, 1987, 1988, 1991, 1994/1995, 1997/1998 (Box 4)
      9th, 10th, 13th, 16th, 19th Annual Editions
    - Black book: International Business and Entertainment Reference Guide, 1994 (Box 4)
    - Success Guide: 1991-1992 Collectors Edition: The Guide to Black Resources, Chicago, 1991 (Box 4)
    - Collectables 1997 Compact Disc & Cassette Catalog, 1997 (Box 4)
      Number 8
    - Fantasy Inc. Catalog, 1987, 1992, 1995-1999 (Box 4)
    - Rhino Catalog, 1993-1994 (Box 4)
      Catalog #15, 18
    - Universal One Stop, February 1996 (Box 4)
    - Gavin: Yellow Pages of Radio, November 11, 1994 (Box 4)
      Issue 2030
    - Schwartz Brothers, Inc. Top Lists and Order Form, January 11, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Big J Records advertisement, undated (Box 4)
    - "The Sound of Young America…is now The Music of the World", 1982 (Box 4)
      Motown Record lists
    - MVD Music Video Distributors catalog, Summer 2000 (Box 4)
    - Jack the Rapper 15th Annual Let's Network Phase IV, 1991 (Box 4)
    - Ground Level, 1996 (Box 4)
      #16
    - Tower Records Special Promotional Catalog, 1996 (Box 4)
    - BMI brochure, 1992 (Box 4)
    - Building Global Brands - Annual Report of Time Warner, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Equipment and Services
    - Universal Record Distributing Corp. Informational Folder, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Ocean Park Studios Brochure (Recording studio), 1982 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Tune Towne Studios Informational Folder, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Color Swatches, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Comprehensive Retail Inventory System (CRIS) Information, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - In-Store Security, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Display Catalogs, ca. 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      Alliances (Spring 1997), JD Store Equipment, Bowers Record Sleeve, United Audio Label Co., Rose Ellis, Homewood Press, POPsmear Postcardz, Eastco Pro, The Color Zone, Color Express, Pen & Pixel Graphics, ON4 Productions
    - Baker & Taylor Informational Folders, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Ross-Ellis Price Lists, September 2005 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - PAM III: Professional Audio Marketplace 1991, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      Third annual survey of equipment and tape used by US audio professionals
    - Audio Equipment Information - Mainly Tape Recording and Duplication, 1982-1990 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      Telex, Akai, Tascam, Electro Sound, Otari, Resolution, Sony, Hitachi TRK-W4H instruction manual, Otari MX80,
    - Audio Equipment Information - Mainly Tape Recording and Duplication, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      Apex, Arcal, Arcoset, Burlington, KABA, Tapematic, Telex
    - Audio Equipment Information - Mainly Consoles, Effects, Synths, 1983-1987, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
      Emax, Oberheim Electronics, Solid State Logic, Soundcraft, SoundTracs, Tascam, Trident, Yamaha
    - Audio Equipment Information - General, 1983-1987, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
      Yamaha, Alpha Audio, Lexicon, Shure, Beyerdynamic
    - Audio Equipment Information - CDs and Digital Recording, 1985-2006, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
      Noble House, Studer Dyaxis, AMS, Masterdisk, Tascam
    - Disc Manufacturing Information, 1988-1998, undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
      Diskmakers, WMG, Allied, Disk Manufacturing (Quixote), Cook Labs, Healey Disc Manufacturing, Safety-sleeve
    - Audio Graphics and Distribution, 1987, 1995-1999, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
      WMG, Wakefield, Sunkyong, QCA, Klarity Kassette, Europadisk, CRT, ICCA, Paulstar Distributing
    - Record Industry Info, 1996, 1998, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Clippings, forms, info sheets
    - Recording Engineering, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Recording Notes and Clippings, 1995, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Broadcasting: Radio, Television, Cable, Satellite, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Magazine clippings and notes
    - Disc Makers booklets, 1993-1999 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Recording/Broadcasting Booklets, 1979-1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Independent Music Association Marketing booklet, Recording Information Association of America statistical overview, National Association of Broadcasters purchasing guide, Association for Independent Music information brochure, MIDI guidebook
    - Federal Communications Commission Broadcast Operator Handbook, March 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - The Independent Record Label Handbook, First Edition, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Published by Datatext
    - The Independent Record Label Handbook, Second Edition, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Recording Pamphlets, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Series III. Publicity and Advertising
  - General
    - Print Outs of Press Releases (1), 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Print Outs of Press Releases (2), 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Print Outs of Press Releases (3), 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Print Outs of Press Releases (4), 1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Print Outs of Press Releases (5), 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - News clippings Binder (1), 1981, 1986-1988, 1990-1994, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - News clippings Binder (2), 1987-1990, 1994-1995, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - News clippings Binder (3), 1982-1990, 1993, 1996, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Slides & Clippings Binder (1), undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Slides & Clippings Binder (2), undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Slides & News Clippings Binder (3), 1981, 1993-2003 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Publicity Photos Binder (1), undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Publicity Photos Binder (2), undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Publicity Photos Binder (3), undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Music Sheets, 1987-1999, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Festival & Reference Pamphlets, 1995-1998, 2008, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - News clippings, 1978-1984, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - CMJ Music Marathon Update, September 21-24, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      Volume 1
    - Release Posters and Notes, 1994-2000 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      Includes a copy of sales article, Wrekology Sprink 1996 program guide
    - Copied Music Data, undated; April 12, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      Ground Level Distribution Hip Hop Catalogue, Billboard radio data
    - Mix Tape Lists, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Track Lists, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Playlists, 1995, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - DJ Materials, 1993, 1995, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      Bios and photocopies
  - Press Packets
    - 263 Records/Bezzle Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - APC Studios, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Basic Concern, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Big Cae Records, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Black Hair Styles and Care Guide, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Bo Deal, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Bossman and the Blakjak, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - The Brew, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - The Bull Fish II, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - C-Side: "myspace.freak" feat. Jazze Pha, 2006; CD-2653 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Dig-It Music, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
      Located with blank cassette tapes in Box 1
    - Disco Houndz, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Down4Life Entertainment, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Down Low Management, Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - DTL: Dyin 2 Live, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - "Durtyville" Bio and Photos, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Easy Entertainment Productions, Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Eternal Warriors, undated; CD-2654 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Fatal Jamz Wrecordz, 1994, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Flow Asylum, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Ful-Meta Multimedia Informational Folder, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - G-Click Management, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - The Graveyards, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Ground Level Distribution New Releases for the Fourth Quarter, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Hollywood Entertainment: "Another Ike & Tina Story", undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - House of Abdul, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - HQH Posse/Tech Sound Records, 1990-1995 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Ital tha Ruffian, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - J-Black, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Joint Mobb, 1995; CD-2655 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Kraftwerk, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Litefoot, 1993-1998 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - LocDown, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Lords of Lyrics, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Mad Street Records, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Major Bank, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - MC R.I.P, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Midwest Records, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Mishon Ratliff, undated; CD-2656 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Murder Dog Media, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Naughty by Nature, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - N'Dambi, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Nexx Level Entertainment, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Nutzo, undated; CD-2657 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - On Mic Productions, undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Parts Unknown, ca. 1995 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Pit Bull Records, Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Power Move, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Rainman, undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Sammy Sam, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Solvizion Entertainment, Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Suicydal (3 folders), undated; CD-2658 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Tape, undated; CD-2659 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Tech Sound Records, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Unyted Music Group, Inc., ca. 1998 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - West Coast Bad Boyz II, 1995, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Wildliffe Society, October 1995 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Witches Brew, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - World Premeire Records papers, undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Young Dose, undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Zero9 Records, undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Mixed Press Materials
    - "One Sheets" (Flyers and Lists), 1997-2000, undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Entertainment Galore, Platinum Bound Promotions, 1986, undated (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Flyers and Photos, 1993, 1999, undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Promotional Materials, 1994-2001, undated (Box 7, Folder 65)
      In a folder labeled "Big J Records".
    - Promotional Materials, 1994-1997, undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
      Recording receipts, posters for The Graveyards, Lil Jon and the East Side Boys & Mic Geronimo, acetate for DJ Jelly and MC Assault, press releases for various artists and record labels.
    - Promotional Materials, 1998-2002, undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
      Includes press releases and articles written by Brian Lassiter.
    - Taxi A&R Informational Folder, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Promotional Materials, 1999, undated (Box 7, Folder 69)
      Major Bank, Joe Cool, Intoxicated, Linx Release Party invitation, Witches Brew photocopy from Elemental, A-Dam-Shame
    - Artist Promotional Materials, 2000, undated (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Promotional Materials, 2001-2006 (Box 7, Folder 71)
      Black Ark Entertainment, Arlinda Garrett, Legal Hustle, Vinnie Brown of Naughty by Nature
    - Khujo Goodie, "The Man, not the Gawg", undated; CD-2660 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Tino Brown, 2002; CD-2661 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - DJ Drama and the Aphiliates, "Hustle and Flows Mixtape", 2006; CD-2888 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Promotional Materials, undated (Box 7, Folder 72)
      Sales Agreement, Big J Records ads, Pub Magazine info, Blaum! Advertising info
    - Promotional Materials, undated (Box 7, Folder 73)
      Press release and photo for Da Nasty Pappy'z, Photos of Joint Mob and Doc J; unlabeled photo.
    - Press Releases - Media World, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Magazines, Newsletters, and Photos
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1992-1998 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Magazine Photocopies, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 76)
      Primarily The Source
    - "The Law Giveth, the Contract Taketh Away" (photocopy), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Magazines, Photocopies, 1996, 2011, undated (Box 7, Folder 78)
      Billboard 2011, Essence fall of 1996, photocopies from various magazines (many Murder Dog)
    - Mr. Baking Soda, "One Life 2 Live", undated; CD-2662 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Army of Two, O Bizzle and Spoon, "It Iz What It Iz", undated; CD-2663 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - The Music Edge - Brochures, Artwork, 1992, 1996, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Luciano Crime Family, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Signed Photo
    - Artist Photos, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Lil' G-lo, Tha M.O.B.B., Blade L, Bad Kat, DATBU, Princess Black
    - Artist Poster Designs, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Envelope of Unlabelled Photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Newsletters, 1990, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      On the Beat Premiere Issue, S Atlanta Report Vol. 2 No. 6
    - Newsletters, 1993-1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      GMA February/March 1998; L.A. Vision January 6, 1993; EQ Tracks; The QCA Quarterly Summer 1999
    - Rolling Out Atlanta, February 10, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Vol. 2 No. 7
    - Hip Hop Magazines, 2004-2010 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Hiphop Encounter #10; Downlow Magazine Vol. 5 Issues 21, 22; Twenty4Seven Issue #6
    - The Streetbuzz magazine, December 2005 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Color Photos - Murder Dog Magazine, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
      Photos by Eric Johnson/ATL
    - DX Magazine Media Kit, January 1997 (Box 8, Folder 11)